

Contact

0336885414

thaihocc.01@gmail.com

fb.com/thaihoc.cao.9/

O Di An, Binh Duong

Overview

Over 3 months of experience in designing and developing web applications and 3 years of experience in embedded programming, designing and manufacturing machines in engineering wire harness for automotive. I would like to be further developed in your career path. Step out of your comfort zone to continue learning, improve knowledge and develop, challenge myself more with software industry. Since then, I want to contribute to developing the company to become more successful.

Skills

- HTML, CSS, Javascript/Typescript.
- React, Redux/Redux tookit, Redux saga.
- Bootstrap, Ant Design, Material UI.
- Knowledge in NodeJs, Angular, Python, Firebase.
- Knowledge in MongoDB, PostgreSQL.
- RESTful API, GraphQL.
- Bitbucket, Jira, Swagger, Postman.
- Team working skills, communications, fast learning ability, creative mind.
- · Work planning.
- Can work under high pressure.
- Can use English in work.

Cao Thái Học

Front End Developer

Education

Ho Chi Minh University Technology and Education

Bachelor of Mechatronics Engineering

2015 - 2020

Grade: Credit

FPT software

Frontend development (ReactJS)

2022 - 2023

Grade: Excellent

Experience

CHIPS JOINT STOCK COMPANY

Web Developer

2/2023 - 5/2023

Main responsibilities:

- Participating in and developing ERP projects.
- Implement UI using ReactJS and AngularJS.
- Coding business logic to create simple API using Python, NodeJS and PostgreSQL, write document API.
- Used Bitbucket for control source code and collaborated with team members

Technical:

ReactJS, Angular, NodeJs, Python, PostgreSQL, API gateway

THERMTROL CORPORATION

Technology Engineer

6/2020 - 10/2022

- Embedded programming to control designed machine.
- Work planning for subordinates, monitor operations to make tools of subordinates, improve immediately any issues and update design drawing accordingly.
- Follow up plans of sample building and new product to design tools on time.
- Review and verify the made tools with Quality Control Engineer to make sure it is good for use or need further improvements/modifications.
- Interface with relative personnel to actively troubleshoot problems as well as continually improve the process.
 Ensure that the goals and objectives are achieved pertain to Safety, Quality, Production, Cost Standards, and Operational Excellence.
- Participate and assist in the development of new process technology, equipment, and projects.

Projects

Website take the quiz

1/2023 - 3/2023

Features such as:

- Sign up, log in, log out
- Refresh token
- Distinguish admin and user
- · Change password, update profile
- Responsive (PC, laptop, Ipad)
- User:
 - Notification when receiving quiz assign from admin (real time)
 - Countdown time when start exam, mark the exam have done(when submit), doing(in time), do not (not started yet)
 - o Countdown time is still counts when you exit or reload, will submit quiz when timeout (in quiz room)
 - o Can restart quiz when quiz don't finish, remind when reload, submit, refresh when quiz don't finish
 - Remind when user tab to another page
 - Mark score the exam, view detailed explanation answers when submit
 - View, search quiz history
- Admin:
 - Manage users (CRUD)
 - Manage quizzes (CRUD)
 - Manage questions
 - o Search user, quiz, question
 - Update question quiz
 - Assign quiz to user

Technical used:

• ReactJS, Bootstrap, Redux, Redux Saga, FireBase, Docker

Motel management system (freelancer)

3/2023 - 5/2023

• Working with API endpoint to created a UI for managing room and cost, electricity and water bill, contract, user authorization, customer support.

Technical used:

• ReactJS, Ant Design, Redux tookit.